Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Building trade unions demand fight on Lewis, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 6: Carnegie Steel workers back union of Lewis, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 7: Complete history of the United Mine Workers of America, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 8: Federation chiefs map fight on CIO, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 9: Garment workers defy the AFL, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 10: Green moves to bring peace in labor ranks, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 11: Green steadfast for Roosevelt despite Lewis, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 12: Green widens rift with CIO in state groups, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 13: J.L. Lewis refuses to talk to Green about CIO peace, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 14: Labor to have its own party, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 15: Peace overtures made to the AFL by CIO leaders, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 16: President greets AFL convention, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 17: Steel workers mildly scolded by AFL head, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 18: Text of John L. Lewis's appeal for the support of Wendell Wilkie, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 19: Unionism and workers, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 20: AFL absorbs big company union, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 21: AFL leaders join in protest on auto strike, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: AFL ultimatum rejected by union, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: AFL unions demand Fisher factory reopen, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: $100,000 is offered to aid steel union, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: AFL absorbs big company union, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: AFL boycotts Hillman's label, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: AFL may start mine union to compete with Lewis's group, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: AFL studies plan for rival mine union to fight Lewis, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: Asserts AFL took 'fatal step', 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 9: CIO faces test in ITU meeting, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 10: CIO unions block peace Parley with committee named by AFL council, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 11: Clothing workers defy AFL order, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 12: Dubinsky appeals for unity of labor, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 13: Green indorses vertical unions where possible, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 14: Green says Lewis blocks federation, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 15: Green sees split in labor widening, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 16: Hillman to aid organization of textile group, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 17: Howard urges rank and file vote on CIO, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 18: Hutcheson, foe of Lewis, quits AFL council, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 19: Insists Brookwood is help to AFL, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 20: Labor in state votes no part in Lewis fight, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 21: Labors civil war, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 22: Lehman pleads with unions to end open rift, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 23: Lewis denies peace is near in AFL fight, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 24: Lewis faction votes to ignore ouster threat, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 25: Millinery union moves to avert split in AFL, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 26: Murray doubts peace prospect in labor split, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 27: Sidelights on current scenes, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 28: Tobin denies AFL rift will hurt Roosevelt, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 29: Unions facing property loss in Lewis split, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 30: AFL convention proceedings summarized, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 31: AFL forces labor rivalry, says Dubinsky, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 32: CIO goes out for 1,000,000, in New England, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 33: Clothiers allot $100,000 to CIO, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: AFL demands large wage rises on recurring basis, 1934-1941 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Farmer-labor national ticket planned in '40, 1934-1941 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: Industrial truce or strife? The labor problem analyzed, 1934-1941 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: Labor in new role Miss Perkins says, 1934-1941 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 5: Labor 'monopoly' upheld by court, 1934-1941 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 6: Labor party lists 320,000 as givers, 1934-1941 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 7: Slaying bares luxurious life of union boss, 1934-1941 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 8: Survey shows 33% of workers in union shops, 1934-1941 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 9: What is unionism's future? A new turn in a vital issue, 1934-1941 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 10: IRT workers warned to shun violent unions, 1934-1941 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: AFL income $1,032,475, expenditures, $975,227, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: AFL to combat Communist boring, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: AFL to fight boring by Reds, council acts today on fur union, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: AFL warned on bar to negroes, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 5: Auto poll shows 69.5% unorganized, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 6: Bill to license business offered by AFL, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 7: Challenge to organized labor, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 8: Coughlin starts motor union to rival AFL, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 9: Frey says unions are necessary to enforce labor legislation, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 10: Grave labor issues facing White House, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 11: Hours of unorganized clerks increase 25 per cent same wages, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 12: How the control dept. functions, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 13: I break strikes, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 14: I break strikes! by P.L. Bergoff, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 15: Labor provisions in trade agreements, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 16: Labor won't stop till 30-hour week is won, says Green, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 17: Leaders cite gains of unions in year, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 18: Progressives and the AFL, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 19: Reports bare wide spread of Peon Labor, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 20: Roar of approval greets forecast of labor's leader, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 21: Senator Long's death is mourned by Green, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 22: South will reopen CIO, Cox asserts, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 23: The vertical union wins, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 24: Toledo labor plan assailed by Green, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 25: Workers cease relationship with automobile labor board, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 26: Green says goal is 30-hour week, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 27: Group here is barred from use of AFL, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 28: Liberties union scores employers, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: AFL and CIO hookup?, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: AFL renews bid for labor merger, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: City employees map legislative fight for new benefits, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Get tough policy is urged by AFL, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Green and Murray rebuke Congress for price 'record', 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: High court rules non-red oaths apply to 'parent' labor unit heads, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Labor in Seattle protests MacArthur visit as 'political', 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Labor unification hinted by Murray, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: New world union maps war on Reds, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Organized labor offers proposals to help fight against inflation, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Pay curbs fought in prices are free, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Spaniard favors AFL-CIO visit, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Talk of a third union federation, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Tobin reassures 'free' worker, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: US labor intercedes for Bolivian miners, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: US labor to omit Yugoslav parley, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Visit of McArthur met by protests, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Labor edges toward the GOP, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: 3 members defend wage body set-up, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: 500 lawyers employed by US labor movement, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: AFL and CIO groups indorse school bonds, 1951; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A case of arbitration, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: AFL and CIO denounce US for abstaining on Tunisian case, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: AFL and CIO in politics go together separately, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: AFL and CIO try to select leaders, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Both AFL and CIO set to name new presidents - merger talk is revived, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: CIO and AFL men fight with knives, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Customs men eye union affiliation, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Farm labor blocs opposed to UMT, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Labor faces election in an uncertain mood, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Labor farm units back foreign aid, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Labor leaders bid union members win 'liberal' congress in Nov., 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Labor turns down Barkley as too old, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Labor's aid grows in welfare work, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Major test snaps AFL-CIO peace, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Move to reduce funeral costs by a union co-operative is begun, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Rival labor chiefs map Chicago plans, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Sitdown Strike laid to US aides, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Truman and Stevenson, bid for the labor vote, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Union press for federal health benefits, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Union split bogs Taft Act change, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Unions ask review of picket decision, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: Unions told to win 'liberal' congress, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: Worst invasion by gangsters since '33 vexes unions here, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: CIO acts to bar defections to AFL, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: The new labor leaders a dual portrait, 1952; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 50,000 parade might of labor, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: AFL and CIO urge heavier profits tax than 4 billion Truman requests, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: AFL gains 13,000 in railroad voting, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: AFL, CIO protest on arms to Arabs, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: AFL, CIO to aid police, firemen, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Candidates defies 'threat' of labor, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: CIO, AFL indorse day's pay gift to community chest, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: City relief study assigned to labor, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Connecticut labor unites for Bowles, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Co-op plan killed by house in voting for 'middle' homes, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Green and Murray to aid fund drive, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Jobless pay seen a political issue, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Labor displease with Democratic line up in state, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Labor groups plan drives to get registrants to polls Tuesday, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Labor joins fight on Marcantonio, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Labor men talk unity action yet to come, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Labor move a help for impellitteri..., 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Picket slow DPW trucks, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Strike threatens industry stoppage, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Tobin and unions cheerful on 1950, Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: Union groups join to bar relief cut, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: Union heads join to aid Red Cross, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: Union merger to be delayed, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: Unity move in labor faces many obstacles, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: US labor opposes aid to Argentina, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: AFL, CIO unite for Taft's defeat, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 27: Labor paraders hear Governor, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 28: Profits and bosses, 1950; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: AFL and CIO negotiators set final stage for December..., 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: AFL and CIO to unite today, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: AFL and CIO will merge, ending 20-year labor split, Meany will head new body, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: AFL takes step without fanfare, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: AFL unanimous for union merger, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: AFL-CIO a harmonious beginning, but, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: AFL-CIO its official now, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: AFL-CIO leader completes 4 standing committees, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: AFL-CIO merger slated in Canada, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: AFL-CIO merger smiles hide scars of former battles, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: AFL-CIO merger stirs labor monopoly charge, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Arabella scenes on disks..., 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Armory crowned by labor meeting, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Author of labor split in 1936..., 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Big Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Challenged labor leader, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: CIO body backs labor unity plan, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: CIO Executive Board approves merger with AFL next week, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: CIO head urges change for 1956, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: CIO-AFL to seek more office unions, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: City may be site of labor merger, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Cleric terms AFL the 'bride' offers 'marital' advice to unions', 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: Construction unions may use welfare fund to rebuild city slums, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: Doubts on unity voiced in AFL, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Eisenhower hears union wage plea, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: Eisenhower's talk excerpts from Meany and Reuther speeches, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: Enlightened labor unionism, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: Harriman attack on GOP bids for AFL-CIO favor, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 29: Harriman scores Eisenhower aides as foes of labor, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: History of labor movement in Country, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 31: Independent unions face effort by mergered union, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 32: Industrial unit of labor set up, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 33: Joint labor eyes role in 1956 race, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 34: Labor and management debate what each wants from other, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 35: Labor and NAM speak, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 36: Labor and politics, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 37: Labor delegates attend church, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 38: Labor joins up, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 39: Labor merger likely to spur organizing, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 40: Labor slate widened, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 41: Labor to remain on Mitchell unit, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 42: Labor unity abroad, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 43: Labor urges ban on funds, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 44: Labor will begin organizing drive, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 45: Labor woos farm bloc?, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 46: Lauds labor bias fight, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 47: Lewis forecasts AFL-CIO split, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 48: Meany backs Moses plea for union owned housing, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 49: Meany blast at Nehru angers India's unions, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 50: Meany charges civil rights blot, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 51: Meany delivers AFL farewell, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 52: Meany outlines labor principles, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 53: Meany says NAM attempts to curb union labor vote, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 54: Meany says Nehru and Tito aid Reds, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 55: Meany vows fight on bias when labors' ranks unite, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 56: Meany's strong leadership acts to centralize AFL, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 57: Merger official, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 58: Merger plans of the Unions and the Leaders' statements, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 59: Merger to bring new union drives, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 60: Mitchell advises amity to labor, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 61: Moses will seek billboard curbs, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 62: NAM aims to destroy labor unions, Meany says in blast at slight, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 63: name is problem to labor merger, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 64: New industrial union dept. organized by AFL-CIO, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 65: New labor body needs organizer, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 66: New York unions to chart merger, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 67: Political oratory beamed upon AFL-CIO, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 68: President reminds labor merger expands its duty, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 69: Problems of labor unity, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 70: Resolutions passed unanimously by AFL-CIO, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 71: Reuther to head industrial unit of combined CIO and AFL, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 72: Stevenson and 2 cabinet men to speak before the first joint labor convention, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 73: Stevenson meets organizers here, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 74: Stevenson outlines political philosophy to labor..., 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 75: Stevenson talk to labor scored, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 76: Text of address given by Stevenson at United Labor Convention..., 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 77: The President to merged labor, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 78: The Resistance, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 79: Tydings says union bars transit plan, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 80: UAW sees merger of AFL-CIO by end of 1955, Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 81: Union designates political chiefs, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 82: Union here begins polio injections, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 83: Union members total 18,000,000, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 84: Union seeks a name, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 85: Union welfare funds, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 86: Unions adopt 'raid' bar, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 87: Unions in drive for membership, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 88: Unions map larger role, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 89: Violence and strikes, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 90: World group may lose India over Meany's blast at Nehru, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 91: $1.25 hourly pay urged by Meany, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 92: 15,000,000-Member AFL-CIO largest Natl. workers group in the free world, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 93: Clean up started by unified labor, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 94: Meany endorses organizing fund, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 95: Meany lays down AFL-CIO policy, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 96: Merger of unions ratified by CIO - 20 year rift ends, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 97: New Haven road sharply rebuked, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 98: President sees Bossism as no AFL-CIO problem, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 99: Quill paves way to enter merger, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 100: Teamsters union meets a barrier, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 101: Union Chiefs say merger creates political strength, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 102: Union heads deny aiming to dictate, 1955; Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 1.1, Folder 5)